Bruno Batista do Nascimento Santos

São Paulo - Brazil

Cell phone: +55 11 959716775

E-mail: brunno1808@hotmail.com

Webpage: https://bbnsdevelop.github.io/brunobatista.github.io/

About me:

With deep experience in system development, I am proactive, self-taught, an evaluator, and a planner. By the way, I believe that organization is the key to everyone's success. I really enjoy micromanaging my tasks. I use techniques such as design patterns, code review, TDD, coverage of unit tests, and agile methodologies to deliver all the projects that I wrap up with quality.

I love teamwork, communicate with my colleagues, and share my knowledge. Absolutely; it is an important step for the team to achieve success. I love supporting new developers as they grow in their careers. I am also certified in the Scrum Foundations Professional Certificate (SFPC). In my opinion, developers must know a little more about that because it allows them to develop and deliver with greater quality.

Technical skill:

Backend:

- Java core, Java 8+, JUNIT and Mockito.
- Spring boot, Sprint data, Spring-Bacth, Spring Cloud, Spring security, JPA, Hibernate.
- Architecture of Microservices, Docker, Kubernets, AWS.
- Databases Oracle SQL, MySql, H2, PostgreSql and MongoDB.
- A litlle Python and NodeJs.

Frontend:

- Angular 2+.
- JavaScript, Jquery, Json, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap.

Others

- Jira, Agile methodologies: SCRUM, Kanban.

Education:

- Bachelor of Computer Science Nove de Julho University.
- Postgraduate Ethical hacking and Cyber security
- Quality Management Flamingo College.

Professional experience:

Fullstack developer Java/Angular Senior at Stefanini - August 2018 - Present

Discuss requirements with the team, prepare technical documents for projects and new functionality, and fix some bugs in production. Meetings with product managers and other stakeholders to discuss project progress and make important decisions.

This project are using tecnologys as:

Architecture microservices with Java 8; Docker; Nginx; Spring data, JDBCTemplate, Spring-Boot, Spring

Cloud, Spring Security, api gateway zuul, Eureka service and client, Postaman; Unitary tests with Junit; Oracle SQL 11;

Code versioning GITLab; Code review; PullRequest; Json;, API Rest and Restful, Maven; Jira; Angular 2 more; HTML5, Bootstrap and Css styler.

The most important thing for me about this project was: I had the opportunity to change from version angular 2 to version 8. Applying the best practices to update the system, such as load balance of modules, Angular Router using route guards, and interceptor requests over HTTP. Migration project On-premise to WAS.

Software engineer java mid at Codelt Solutions - of 2018 until 2018.

Analytics and development system with agile method. This project are using tecnologys as: Architecture microservices with Java 8; Docker; Spring data, JDBCTemplate, Spring-Boot, Spring Cloud, Spring Security, api gateway zuul, Eureka service and client, Postaman; Unitary tests with Junit; Oracle SQL 11;

Code versioning GITLab; Code review; PullRequest; Json;, API Rest and Restful, Maven; Jira; Angular 4; HTML5, Bootstrap and Css styler.

Software engineer java mid at Banck Santander - of 2017 until 2018

Development and Analysis of APIs for the banking sector using technologies: Java 7 and8; Hibernate, JPA, Spring Boot, Spring-Bacth, Spring Cloud, Apache TomCat 6, Apache TomCat 7, Apache TomCat 8, Oracle SQL, GIT, JSON, SOAPUI, REST, MAVEN, Micro applications, Micro Services, Integrations with external systems, Agile methodologies: SCRUM.

Analyst / Developer java fullStack jr At Stefanini - of 2016 until 2017.

Customer: Bank Original

Requirements gathering, understanding demands, maintenance, development and Analysis of banking systems interfaces in JSP, html5, JSF, Java-Script, Jquery, Ajax, Angularjs, Java 7; Hibernate, JPA, Spring FrameWork, Spring-Bacth, ApacheTomCat 6, Apache TomCat 7, Oracle SQL, GIT, JSON, SOAPUI, REST, MAVEN:

Customer: Bank - Bradesco

Responsible for organizing, maintaining, developing and automating systems banking interfaces in JSP, Servlets, javascript Java 5, Jsf 2.0, primefaces, Webservice, AWB 2, StarTeam, WinMerge, pdc-ejb-1.3, myfaces-all-1.1.1, richfaces. Carrying out the creation of unit and integrated tests, preparation of documents for software, test scripting.

Java Developer / Analyst jr at BRQ IT Services - of 2014 until 2015.

Bank - Bradesco

Development and maintenance of IT solutions system for the financial market - using Java JEE, JSF, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Tomcat, communication with MainFrame, MyFaces, Tomahawk, Prime Faces, Systems integration with web services. Reports with JasperReport.